[
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is correct about TypeScript?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Angular 2 is based on TypeScript.",
            "This is a superset of JavaScript.",
            "TypeScript is maintained by Microsoft.",
            "All of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "All of the above"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following is true?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Angular 2 Modules are used to create components which can be shared across the entire application.",
            "Angular 2 Metadata is used to create components which can be shared across the entire application.",
            "Angular 2 Services are used to create components which can be shared across the entire application.",
            "None of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Angular 2 Services are used to create components which can be shared across the entire application."
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following is correct about Export Array in Angular 2 Modules?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "This is used to export components, directives, and pipes which can then be used in other modules.",
            "This is used to export services which can then be used in other services.",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "This is used to export components, directives, and pipes which can then be used in other modules."
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following is correct about Angular 2 Routing?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Routing helps in directing users to different pages based on the option they choose on the main page.",
            "Based on the option they choose, the required Angular Component will be rendered to the user.",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Both of the above"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which of the following filter is used to convert an input string to date format.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "dateformat",
            "date",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "date"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Angular 2 components can be described using ________is a way to do some meta-programming.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "controllers, controller",
            "loaders, loader",
            "typescripts, typescript",
            "decorators, decorator"
        ],        
        "answer" : "decorators, decorator"
    },
	{
        "question" : "The ______ directive substitutes the normal href property and makes it easier to work with route links in Angular 2.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "RouterRend",
            "RouterLink",
            "RouterLike",
            "RouterLayer"
        ],        
        "answer" : "RouterLink"
    },
	{
        "question" : "A special mention is required about the children element marked with the ______ directive attribute. This attribute qualifies the template that will be displayed when no other value defined by its ngSwitchWhen siblings matches the parent conditional expression.",
        "options" : 
        [
            "ngDefault",
            "ngTemplateDefault",
            "ngDefaultSwitch",
            "ngSwitchDefault"
        ],        
        "answer" : "ngSwitchDefault"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Using below wild card we can define page not found route",
        "options" : 
        [
            "*",
            "**",
            "404",
            "!"
        ],        
        "answer" : "**"
    },
	{
        "question" : "A component can have child route defined using below property",
        "options" : 
        [
            "routes",
            "children",
            "routeCollection",
            "None of the above"
        ],        
        "answer" : "children"
    }
]